A Finding Aid to the LeRoy Neiman Papers, 1938-2005, in the Archives of American Art AAA.neimlero
Archives of American Art
Elayne Galleries - 2.1: 1979, 1989, 3.1: Elayne Galleries and P.J. Clarke's, 1978, 3.1: Stadium Tennis Billboard, 1981, 4.1: 2001, see also exhibitions
elephant paintings - see animals
Elkins Entertainment - 3.1: Rhythm and Smoke Cigar Video, 1997
Elles & Eux Magazine - 4.1: 1961
Ellington, Duke - see jazz
Ellis, Jimmy - 4.1: 1971
Ellis Island Medal of Honor - 1.1: Awards
Elway, John - 3.1: John Elway, 1999
Emerald Art Gallery - 2.1: 1977, 3.1: Emerald Art Gallery Solo Exhibition 1976
English, John - 1.1: Military Service
equestrian - see horses
Erte - 4.1: 1990, 1980s and 1990s (mentioned throughout)
Erving, Julius - see Basketball Superstars, 1975-76, Julius Erving, 1975 - 3.1: Julius Erving 1975-76
Esposito, Frank - see bowling
Esposito, Phil - 4.1: 1975
Esquire Magazine - 2.1: 1999, 3.1: Dewar's Profile 1970 ov, 4.1: 1999
Estefan, Emilio and Gloria - 2.1: 1984
etchings - 2.1: 1977, 3.1: Malletmen etching Certificate, 1977, 1.2: Bowles Galleries Correspondence 1970s, see also boxing: Ali vs. Frazier II etchings, 1974, and soccer: Soccer, 1989 etching, The Etchings of LeRoy Neiman, 1976 Knoedler booklet - 3.1: The Etchings of LeRoy Neiman, 1976 booklet (ov)
Eve Models, Ltd. - 4.1: 1971, 1974
Everson, Cory - see bodybuilding
Evert, Chris - see tennis
Ewbank, Weeb - 3.1: Gridiron Football News 1971-1973, 4.1: 1978
exhibitions - Note: Solo and group exhibitions are listed alphabetically by the venue name
solo exhibitions
750 Studio, Chicago, 1953 - 3.1: 750 Studio, Chicago, Solo Exhibition 1953
Abercrombie & Fitch, 1974 - 4.1: 1974
Allyson Louis Gallery, Bethesda, MD, 1988 - 3.1: Superbowl XXII painting In the Pocket, at Allyson Louis Gallery 1988
Allyson Louis Gallery, Bethesda, MD, 1990 - 4.1: 1990, V: 1990
American Fine Art Editions, Inc., "Superbowl XXX," Jan 1996 - 3.1: Superbowl XXX Exhibition 1996
American Fletcher National Bank - see Indianapolis Museum of Art
l'art et l'automobile gallery, "Monte Carlo Chase," New York 1988 - 3.2. Monte Carlo Chase, 1988, Van Der Marck Editions, Ltd., Related Exhibitions
l'art et l'automobile gallery, New York, 1989 - no materials
The Art Exchange, Creve Coeur, MO, 1978 - 3.1: The Art Exchange Solo Exhibitions, Creve Coeur, MO 1978-79
The Art Exchange, Creve Coeur, MO, 1979 - 3.1: The Art Exchange Solo Exhibitions, Creve Coeur, MO 1978-79
Art Gallery-Studio 53 Ltd., New York 1975 - 4.1: 1975
Art Gallery-Studio 53 Ltd., New York 1976 - 4.1: 1976
Astor Tower French Center, Chicago, "Vie de France," 1965 - 3.1: "Vie de France" Solo Exhibition, Astor Tower, Chicago 1965
Backstage Gallery, Osaka, Japan - 4.1: 1989
Baja - 4.1: 1989
Base Art Collection, 1990 - 4.1: 1990
Bowles/Hopkins Gallery, San Francisco, 1977 - 3.1: Bowles Hopkins Solo Exhibition, San Francisco, 1977
Bowles/Hopkins Gallery, San Francisco, 1980 - 2.1: 1980, 4.1: 1980
Bowles/Hopkins Gallery, San Francisco 1981 - 4.1: 1981
Bowles/Hopkins Gallery show celebrating Winners, 1983 - 3.2. Winners, 1983, Harry N. Abrams
Bowles/Hopkins Gallery, "The Olympic Spirit," San Francisco, 1984 - 3.1: 1984 Olympics
Bowles/Hopkins Gallery show celebrating the Superbowl, 1985 - 4.1: 1985
Bowles/Hopkins Gallery, February 1986 - 3.1: Nob Hill, Buena Vista and Bowles Hopkins Gallery 1986
Bowles/Hopkins Gallery, October 1986 - 3.1: Nob Hill, Buena Vista and Bowles Hopkins Gallery 1986
Bowles/Sorokko Galleries, "Neiman's Neimans: A Retrospective," San Francisco, 1987 - 3.1: Bowles/Sorokko Galleries Solo Exhibitions, San Francisco ("Neiman's Neimans") and Beverly Hills 1987
Bowles/Sorokko Galleries, Beverly Hills 1987 - 3.1: Bowles/Sorokko Galleries Exhibition, Beverly Hills 1987
Bowles/Sorokko Galleries, "LeRoy Neiman: Monte Carlo," San Francisco 1988 - 3.2. Monte Carlo Chase, 1988, Van Der Marck Editions, Ltd., Related Exhibitions
Bowles/Sorokko Galleries, Polo Lounge Debut, Beverly Hills, April 1989 - 3.1: Polo Lounge debut at Bowles/Sorokko Galleries, Beverly Hills 1989
Bowles/Sorokko Galleries, San Francisco, May 1990 - 3.1: Bay Area Baseball debut at Bowles/Sorokko, San Francisco 1990
Bowles/Sorokko, Beverly Hills, October 1990 - 4.1: 1990
Bowles/Sorokko Galleries, "The Prints of LeRoy Neiman 1980 -1990," Beverly Hills, 1991 - 3.2. The Prints of LeRoy Neiman, 1980-1990, 1991
Bowles/Sorokko Galleries, "LeRoy Neiman's San Francisco," San Francisco 1991 - 3.1: San Francisco Series 1991-93
Bowles/Sorokko Galleries, "LeRoy Neiman: Downtown," New York 1992 - 4.1: 1992
Bowles/Sorokko Galleries, "Big Time Golf," Beverly Hills, San Francisco, and New York, 1992 - 3.2. Big Time Golf, 1992, Publicity and Related Exhibitions
Bowles/Sorokko Galleries, City by the Bay Debut, San Francisco, 1993 - 3.1: San Francisco Series, 1991-1993
Bowles/Sorokko Galleries, "An American in Paris," Beverly Hills, San Francisco, and New York, 1994 - 3.2. LeRoy Neiman: An American in Paris, 1994, Related Exhibitions
Bowles/Sorokko Galleries, San Francisco, 1995 - 4.1: 1995
Bowles/Sorokko/Yarger Galleries, "Portraits of Our Times 1946-1996", Beverly Hills and San Francisco 1996 - 3.1: "Portraits of Our Times 1946-96" Solo Exhibition and Catalog, Bowles/Sorokko/Yarger Galleries, 1996
Brentano's Gallery, New York, 1973 - 4.1: 1973
Brentano's Gallery, New York, 1979 - 2.1: 1979, 4.1: 1979
Brentano's Gallery, New York, 1980 - 4.1: 1980
Butler Institute of American Art, Exhibition at "The Art Spirit" Event, April 1990 - 4.1: 1990
Carol Condit Galleries, White Plains, 1975 - 4.1: 1975
Casa Grafica, Helsinki, Finland, 1977 - 3.1: Casa Grafica Solo Exhibition, Helsinki, Finland, 1977
"Celebration 2000," 2000 - 3.2. The Prints of LeRoy Neiman, 1991-2000, 2001
Centaur Galleries, Las Vegas, 2000 - 4.1: 2000
Centaur Sculpture Galleries, "The Safari Suite," Las Vegas 1996 - 3.2. LeRoy Neiman On Safari, 1996, Related Exhibitions
Center Art Galleries, Honolulu, Hawaii, 1985 - 3.1: Center Art Galleries Exhibition, Hawaii, 1985
Chabot Galleries, 1984 - 4.1: 1984
Choate School, "LeRoy Neiman: Paintings and Drawings," 1969 - 4.1: 1969
Circle Gallery, Chicago 1972 - 3.1: Circle Gallery Solo Exhibition, Chicago, 1972
Circle Galleries Los Angeles, Dallas, and NYC, 1973 - 3.1: Circle Galleries Los Angeles, Dallas, NYC, 1973
Circle Gallery, New York, "Ali - Frazier," 1974 - 3.1: Ali vs. Frazier I, 1971
Dean Day Gallery, 1983 - 4.1: 1982, 1983
Dyansen Gallery, "The Playboy Collection," 1989-90 - 3.1: Dyansen Gallery Playboy Collection touring exhibition 1989-90
Dyansen Gallery, Trump Taj Mahal, 1992 - 3.1: Dyansen Gallery Solo Exhibition, Atlantic City, and The Beatles serigraph 1992
Elayne Galleries, Minneapolis, MN, 1978 - 3.1: Elayne Galleries Solo Exhibition and P.J. Clarkes, Minneapolis, 1978
Emerald Art Gallery, Coronado, CA, 1976 - 3.1: Emerald Art Gallery Solo Exhibition, Coronado, CA 1976
Fairfield Gallery, "LeRoy Neiman - A Retrospective Exhibition of Works on Paper," 2001 - 3.1: "LeRoy Neiman - A Retrospective Exhibition of Works on Paper," Fairfield Gallery, 2001
Fahlnaes Konstsalong, Sweden, 1976 - 3.1: Sweden Exhibitions 1976-77
Famous-Barr, St. Louis, MO, 1980 - 3.1: Famous-Barr Olympic Benefit Solo Exhibition, St. Louis 1980
The Far Gallery, "Recent Graphics and Drawings", 1971 - 3.1: "Recent Graphics and Drawings," The Far Gallery Solo Exhibition 1971
Fingerhut Gallery, La Jolla, CA, 2003 - 4.1: 2003
Forsyth Gallery, St. Louis, MO, 1970 - 4.1: 1970
Foster Harmon Galleries, Sarasota, 1980 - 4.1: 1980, V: 1980
Foster Harmon Galleries, Sarasota, 1981 - 4.1: 1981
Foster Harmon Galleries, Sarasota, 1986 - 4.1: 1986
Foster Harmon Galleries, Sarasota, 1992 - 4.1: 1992
Franklin Bowles Galleries, "Animals: The Wild and the Tame", 1998 - 3.1: "Animals: The Wild and the Tame" Solo Exhibition, Franklin Bowles Gallery, San Francisco, October 1998
Franklin Bowles Galleries, "LeRoy Neiman: Master Printmaker," 2001 - 3.1: "LeRoy Neiman: Master Printmaker," Franklin Bowles Gallery, San Francisco 2001
Frankin Bowles Galleries, "LeRoy Neiman: Thirty Years in San Francisco," 2002 - 3.1: "LeRoy Neiman: Thirty Years in San Francisco," Franklin Bowles Galleries, San Francisco 2002
Franklin Bowles Galleries, "Looking Back: The Life & Times of America's Artist", Fisherman's Wharf, San Francisco, February 2004 - 4.1: 2004
Franklin Bowles Galleries, "LeRoy Neiman: The Art of Boxing," San Francisco, February 2005 - 3.1: "LeRoy Neiman: The Art of Boxing," Franklin Bowles Galleries 2005
Friars Club, 1987 - see exhibitions: New York Friars Club
Galerie 224, 1989 - 4.1: 1989
Galerie Borjeson, Malmo, Sweden, 1976 - 3.1: Sweden Exhibitions 1976-77
Galerie O. Bosc, Paris 1962 - 4.1: 1962
Galerie Marc, San Francisco, 1977 - 4.1: 1977
Galerie Marcel Bernheim, "Un Américain à Paris," Paris 1993 - 3.1: "Un Américain à Paris," Solo Exhibition, Galerie Marcel Bernheim, Paris 1993
Galerie Renee & Victor, Stockholm, Sweden, 1977 - 3.1: Sweden Exhibitions 1976-77
La Galleria d'Arte, Newport Beach, CA, 1993 - 2.2: La Galleria d'Arte, 4.1: 1993, V: 1993
La Galleria d'Arte, "An American in Paris," Newport Beach, CA, 1994 - 2.2: La Galleria d'Arte, 3.2. LeRoy Neiman: An American in Paris, 1994, Related Exhibitions
La Galleria d'Arte, "LeRoy Neiman On Safari," Newport Beach, CA 1996 - 2.2: La Galleria d'Arte, 3.2. LeRoy Neiman On Safari, 1996, Related Exhibitions
Gallery One American Design, Aurora, Colorado, August 1990 - 3.1: Gallery One Solo Exhibition, Denver, Colorado, 1990
Gallery One of Writer Square, Denver, August 1990 - 3.1: Emerson Fittipaldi, 1989, 3.1: Gallery One Solo Exhibition, Denver, Colorado, 1990
Gallery 36, New York, 1973 - 4.1: 1973
Gallery 100, Mishawaka, IN, 1977 - 4.1: 1977
Gallery Hawaii, International Market Place, 1974 - 3.1: Hawaii and Japan 1974
Gallery Hawaii, Hyatt Regency, 1976 - 4.1: 1976
Gallery Mack, Seattle, 1978 - 3.1: Gallery Mack Solo Exhibition, Seattle 1978
Gallery Mack, "Drawings by LeRoy Neiman: A Retrospective," Seattle, 1981 - 3.1: Neiman/Warhol Exhibition at LAICA 1981-82
Gallery Mack, Seattle, 1982 - 3.1: Gaylord Perry's 300th win 1982
Gallery of Modern Art, Frank Sinatra drawings, New York, 1967 - 3.1: Frank Sinatra Film Drawings Exhibition, Gallery of Modern Art 1967
Gallery Richelle, 1966 - 4.1: 1966
Gateway Gallery, Vail, CO, 1994 - 4.1: 1994
Gilbert Gallery, San Francisco, 1974 - 4.1: 1974
Grigsby Gallery, Scottsdale, AZ, 1982 - 4.1: 1982
Hammer Galleries, 1963 - 3.1: Hammer Galleries Solo Exhibition 1963
Hammer Galleries, 1965 - 3.1: Hammer Galleries Solo Exhibition 1965
Hammer Galleries, 1967 - 3.1: Hammer Galleries Solo Exhibition 1967
Hammer Galleries Exhibition of New York Jets Drawings, 1968 - 3.1: Hammer Galleries Exhibition of NY Jets Drawings, 1968
Hammer Galleries, 1970 - 3.1: Hammer Galleries Solo Exhibition 1970
Hammer Galleries, 1972 - 3.1: Hammer Galleries Solo Exhibition 1972
Hammer Galleries, 1974 - 4.1: 1974
Hammer Galleries, "LeRoy Neiman: Works on Paper," 1975-76 - 3.1: Hammer Galleries Solo Exhibition 1975-76
Hammer Galleries, "The Olympic Ring," 1976 - 3.1: 1976 Olympics, Montreal
Hammer Galleries, "Horses," 1979-80 - 3.2. Horses, 1979, Harry N. Abrams, Publicity, Reviews, and Related Exhibitions
Hammer Galleries, "Drawings: A Retrospective," 1981 - 3.1: "Drawings" A Retrospective" Solo Exhibition, Hammer Galleries 1981
Hammer Galleries, 1982 - 4.1: 1982
Hammer Galleries, "LeRoy Neiman: Winners," 1983 - 3.2. Winners, 1983, Harry N. Abrams, Publicity and Related Exhibitions; Photos, Proofs, and BLAD
Hammer Galleries, "The Olympics, Past and Present," 1984 - 3.1: 1984 Olympics, Los Angeles
Hammer Galleries, "The LeRoy Neiman Collection," 1985 - 3.1: "The LeRoy Neiman Collection" Exhibition, Hammer Galleries, 1985
Hammer Galleries, "LeRoy Neiman in Moscow," April 1987 - 3.1: "LeRoy Neiman in Moscow" Solo Exhibition, Hammer Galleries 1987
Hammer Galleries, "Soft Paintings," April 1989 - 3.1: Soft Paintings 1989
Hammer Galleries, "LeRoy Neiman: A Salute to Central Park," September 1989 - 3.1: "A Salute to Central Park" Solo Exhibition, Hammer Galleries 1989
Hammer Galleries, "Big Time Golf," 1992 - 3.2. Big Time Golf, 1992, Publicity and Related Exhibitions
Hammer Galleries, "An American in Paris," 1994 - 3.2. LeRoy Neiman: An American in Paris, 1994, Related Exhibitions
Hammer Galleries, "LeRoy Neiman On Safari," New York, 1996 - 3.2. LeRoy Neiman On Safari, 1996, Related Exhibitions
Hammer Galleries, "A View from the Table," Solo Exhibition, New York, 2003 - 3.1: "A View from the Table" Solo Exhibition, Hammer Galleries, New York, 2003
Hammer Graphics Gallery, 1979 - 3.1: Hammer Graphics Gallery Solo Exhibition 1979
Hammer Graphics Gallery exhibition of graphic works 1971-81, 1981 - 4.1: 1981
Hanae Mori Building, "Neiman's World - Japan '88," Tokyo, 1988 - 3.1: "Neiman's World" Exhibition, Japan 1988
Hang-Up Gallery, 1973 - 4.1: 1973 and ov
Hanson Art Galleries, New Orleans, 1983-84 - 3.1: Hanson Art Galleries Solo Exhibitions, New Orleans and Carmel, 1983-84
Hanson Art Galleries, Carmel, CA, 1984 - 3.1: Hanson Art Galleries Solo Exhibitions, New Orleans and Carmel, 1983-84
Hanson Art Galleries, La Jolla, 1986 - 3.1: Hanson Art Galleries Solo Exhibition, La Jolla, 1986
Hanson Art Galleries, San Francisco, 1987 - 3.1: Hanson Art Galleries Solo Exhibition, San Francisco Bay Area, 1987
Hanson Art Galleries, New Orleans, 1997 - 3.1: Hanson Art Galleries Solo Exhibition, New Orleans 1997
Hanson Art Galleries, New Orleans, 1998 - 4.1: 1998
Hanson Art Galleries, "A Decade of Retrospective Works by LeRoy Neiman," 2000 - 3.1: "A Decade of Retrospective Works by LeRoy Neiman" 2000
Harrod's, London, 1982 - 3.1: Harrod's Gallery Solo Exhibition, London 1982
Heath Gallery, "LeRoy Neiman: Impressions of Atlanta", Atlanta, GA, 1969 - 4.1: 1969
Heit Galleries, Phoenix, AZ, 1976 - 3.1: Heit Galleries Solo Exhibition, Phoenix 1976
Nicholas Helion, Paris, 1980 - 4.1: 1980
Hess's Gallery, Allentown, PA, 1975 - 3.1: Hess's Gallery Solo Exhibition, Allentown, PA, 1975
Hilliard Gallery, Kansas City, October 1989 - V: 1989
Hilliard Gallery, "The Safari Suite," Kansas City, MO, 1996 - 3.2. LeRoy Neiman On Safari, 1996, Related Exhibitions
Horizon Gallery, Kuhio Mall, Waikiki Beach 1980 - 4.1: 1980 and ov
Hotrod Vintage Car Museum and Dance Club, 1989 - 4.1: 1989
Indianapolis Museum of Art, "Sketches of the XXth Olympiad," Miliken Gallery, 1972-73 - 3.1: "Sketches of the XXth Olympiad," Solo Exhibition, Indianapolis Museum of Art, 1972-73
Indianapolis Museum of Art, Downtown Gallery at American Fletcher National Bank, 1976 - 2.1: 1976, 3.1: Indianapolis Museum of Art Solo Exhibition 1976
Japan - see exhibitions: Backstage Gallery, exhibitions: Hanae Mori Building and exhibitions: Tobu Gallery
Jewish Community Center, Bridgeport, CT, 1976 - 4.1: 1976
JoAnn Perse Gallery, Little Rock, 1983 - 3.2. Winners, 1983, Harry N. Abrams
JoAnn Perse Gallery, "Monte Carlo Chase," Little Rock 1988 - 3.2. Monte Carlo Chase, 1988, Van Der Marck Editions, Ltd., Related Exhibitions
John Miller Gallery, Carmel, CA 1982 - 4.1: 1982
Kentucky Derby Museum, "An Exhibition of Equine Art," 1993 - 3.1: "Equine Art" and "Racing Retrospective" Solo Exhibitions, Kentucky Derby Museum 1993-95
Kentucky Derby Museum, "A Racing Retrospective," 1995 - 3.1: "Equine Art" and "Racing Retrospective" Solo Exhibitions, Kentucky Derby Museum 1993-95
Kentucky Derby Museum, "The Art of Sport," 1997 - 3.1: 123rd Kentucky Derby and Derby Day Paddock 1997
M. Knoedler & Co., Ltd., London, 1976 - 3.1: Knoedler London Solo Exhibition 1976 Krannert School of Management, 1986 - no materials
Lawrence Ross Galleries, Beverly Hills, 1985 - 3.1: Lawrence Ross Galleries 1985-88
Lawrence Ross Galleries, Beverly Hills, 1986 - 3.1: Lawrence Ross Galleries 1985-88
Lincoln College, 1953 - 4.1: 1953
Marlborough Galleries, Boston, 1987 - 3.1: Marlborough Galleries Exhibition, Boston 1987
Mayfair Art Gallery, Saratoga Springs, NY, 1977 - 2.1: 1977
Meredith Long & Company, Houston, 1975 - 4.1: 1975
Meredith Long & Company, Houston, 1978 - 4.1: 1978
Merrill Chase Galleries, Chicago, 1976 - 4.1: 1976
Merrill Chase Galleries, Chicago, 1978 - 4.1: 1978 and ov
Merrill Chase Galleries, Chicago, 1982 - 4.1: 1982
Merrill Chase Galleries, Chicago, 1988 - 4.1: 1988
Merrill Chase Galleries, "Big Time Golf," Chicago 1992 - 3.2. Big Time Golf, 1992, Publicity and Related Exhibitions
Merrill Chase Galleries, "An American in Paris," Chicago 1994 - 3.2. LeRoy Neiman: An American in Paris, 1994, Related Exhibitions
Merrill Chase Galleries, "The Safari Suite," Chicago 1996 - 3.2. LeRoy Neiman On Safari, 1996, Related Exhibitions
Merv Griffin Resorts International Casino Hotel, Atlantic City, 1990 - 3.1: Merv Griffin's Resorts Casino Exhibition 1990
Midwest Museum of Art, "Selected Works by LeRoy Neiman", 1989 - 3.1: Midwest Museum of Art Exhibition, 1989
Minnesota Museum of Art, "LeRoy Neiman Retrospective," St. Paul, 1975-76 - 3.1: St. Paul Bicentennial 1975-76
Minotaur Galleries, Las Vegas 1983 - 2.2: Minotaur Galleries 1984-1994, 4.1: 1983
Minotaur Galleries, Las Vegas 1984 - 2.2: Minotaur Galleries 1984-1994, 4.1: 1984
Minotaur Galleries, Las Vegas 1985 - 2.2: Minotaur Galleries 1984-1994, 4.1: 1985
Minotaur Galleries, Las Vegas 1988 - 2.2: Minotaur Galleries 1984 -1994, 3.2. Monte Carlo Chase, 1988, Related Exhibitions, Van Der Marck Editions, Ltd., 4.1: 1988
Minotaur Galleries, "Big Time Golf," Las Vegas 1992 - 3.2. Big Time Golf, 1992, Publicity and Related Exhibitions
Minotaur's Forum Gallery, Las Vegas 1993 - 2.2: Minotaur Galleries 1984-1994, 4.1: 1993
Museo de Bellas Artes, Caracas, 1972 - 2.1: 1972, 4.1: 1972, V: 1970s
Myrtle Todes Gallery, Glencoe, Illinois, 1957 - 3.1: Myrtle Todes Gallery Solo Exhibition, Glencoe, Illinois 1957
National Art Museum of Sport, "LeRoy Neiman: Works on Paper," 2001 - 3.1: "LeRoy Neiman: Works on Paper," National Art Museum of Sport, 2001
Nevada County Arts Council, 1982 - 4.1: 1982
New York Friars Club, 1987 - 3.1: New York Friars Club Solo Exhibition, 1987
Niagara Art Center, Niagara Falls, 1976 - 4.1: 1976
O'Hana Gallery, London, 1962 - 3.1: O'Hana Gallery Solo Exhibition, London 1962
F. Oehlschlaeger Gallery, Chicago 1959 - 3.1: Frank Oehlschlaeger Gallery Solo Exhibition, Chicago 1959
F. Oehlschlaeger Gallery, Chicago, 1961 - 4.1: 1961
F. Oehlschlaeger Gallery, Chicago, 1962 - no material
F. Oehlschlaeger Gallery, Chicago 1976 - 4.1: 1976
Oklahoma Art Center Sheets Gallery, "Drawings by LeRoy Neiman: A Retrospective," 1981 - 3.1: "Drawings by LeRoy Neiman," Oklahoma Art Center 1981
Paterson Museum, Paterson, NJ, 1996 - 2.1: 1989, 4.1: 1996
Percival Galleries, Des Moines, 1979 - 2.1: 1978, 1979, 4.1: 1979
Peri-Renneth Gallery, Southampton, 1986 - 3.1: Peri-Reneth Gallery Solo Exhibition 1986
Peter Foulger Museum, Nantucket, 1975 - 3.2. Moby Dick, 1975, The Artist's Limited Edition
Playboy offices, "LeRoy Neiman: Man at his Leisure" 1991 - V: 1991
Pratt Institute, "LeRoy Neiman in Cuba," 2003 - 3.1: "LeRoy Neiman in Cuba" Solo Exhibition, Pratt Institute, New York, 2003
"Profiles: Six Decades of Work" 1996 - 3.1: "Profiles" Exhibition 1996
Purdue University, 1986 - 4.1: 1986
Quinn-Pollak Gallery, "Monte Carlo Chase," San Diego 1988 - 3.2. Monte Carlo Chase, 1988, Van Der Marck Editions, Ltd., Related Exhibitions
Richelle Gallery, St. Louis, 1966 - see Gallery Richelle
Rosenbaum Galleries, Palm Beach, 1976 - 2.1: 1976, 4.1: 1976
St. Lawrence National Bank, 1977 - 3.1: St. Lawrence National Bank Solo Exhibition, Ogdensburg, NY, 1977
Sher Gallery, Florida, 1986 - 4.1: 1986
Springfield Art Association, "LeRoy Neiman: A Series of Sport Serigraphs," Springfield, IL, 1990 - 4.1: 1990
Springfield College - 3.1: LeRoy Neiman Centennial Art Exhibition, Springfield, MA, 1984
Springfield Museum of Art, 1974 - 4.1: 1974
State National Bank, El Paso, 1981 - 4.1: 1981
Steiner & Young Fine Arts Galleries, 1989 - 3.1: Steiner & Young Galleries Exhib 1989, 3.1: Soft Paintings 1989, 3.2. Monte Carlo Chase, 1988, Van Der Marck Editions, Ltd., Related Exhibitions
Surf Club, 1989 - 4.1: 1989
Thomas Ward Galleries, St. Paul, 1975 - 4.1: 1975
Timothy Yarger Fine Art, "The Culinary Arts" 1998 - 3.1: "The Culinary Arts" Solo Exhibition, Timothy Yarger Fine Art, Beverly Hills 1998
Timothy Yarger Fine Art, "A Thirty-Year Retrospective Exhibition" - 3.1: Timothy Yarger Fine Art, "A Thirty -Year Retrospective" Exhibition 2000
Timothy Yarger Fine Art, "LeRoy Neiman: A Fifty-Year Retrospective", Beverly Hills, 2003 - 3.2. LeRoy Neiman: Five Decades, 2003
The Toy Store, Hartford, CT, 1985 and 1986 - 3.1: The Toy Store 1985-86
Tobu Gallery, Tokyo, 1974 - 3.1: Hawaii and Japan 1974
Tretyakov Museum, Moscow 1988 - 3.1: Tretyakov Museum Solo Exhibition, Moscow 1988
Trump Plaza, Atlantic City, 1996 - 3.2. LeRoy Neiman: An American in Paris, 1994, Correspondence
Turnbery Isle Yacht and Racquet Club Exhibition, 1981, 1982, 1983 - 3.1: Turnberry Isle Yacht and Racquet Club Exhibitions 1981-83
Edwin A. Ulrich Museum of Art, Wichita State University, 1981 - 2.1: 1981
University of Charleston, West Virginia, Art Gallery, 1992 - 4.1: 1992
Upstairs Gallery, Beverly Hills, 1977 - 4.1: 1977
Upstairs Gallery, Beverly Hills, 1981 - 4.1: 1981
Upstairs Gallery, Beverly Hills, Exhibition celebrating Winners, 1983 - 3.2. Winners, 1983, Harry N. Abrams, Publicity and Related Exhibitions
Upstairs Gallery, Beverly Hills, 1986 - 4.1: 1986
Upstairs Gallery, Beverly Hills, 1987 - 4.1: 1987
Upstairs Gallery, Beverly Hills, 1988 - 4.1: 1988
Waller's Gallery, Tampa, 1975 - 4.1: 1975
Wichita State University Ulrich Museum of Art Exhibition 1981 - 4.1: 1981
The Wildlife Experience, "LeRoy Neiman on Safari," 2003 - 3.1: "LeRoy Neiman on Safari" Solo Exhibition, The Wildlife Experience, Parker, CO, 2003
Windsor Gallery, Los Angeles, 1974 - 3.1: Windsor Gallery Solo Exhibitions, Los Angeles 1974-75
Windsor Gallery, "The Wide World of LeRoy Neiman," Los Angeles, 1975 - 3.1: Windsor Gallery Solo Exhibitions, Los Angeles 1974-75
two-person exhibitions
LeRoy Neiman and Robert Addison, Art Institute of Chicago, 1978 - 4.1: 1978 and ov
Alexander Calder and LeRoy Neiman, Nassau Gallery, Baldwin, NY 1973 - 4.1: 1973
"The Mustache Show", Salvador Dali and LeRoy Neiman, Tunnel Club, New York, 1988 - 3.1: Baird Jones' Group Exhibitions, New York 1988-89
LeRoy Neiman/Andy Warhol, LAICA, Los Angeles 1981 - 3.1: Neiman/ Warhol Exhibition 1981
group exhibitions
Amherst College, "When They Were Very Young," Amherst, MA 1982 - 4.1: 1982
Amnesty International Exhibition and Sale, New York, 1990 - 4.1: 1990
Anna Werbe Gallery, Chicago Artists, Detroit 1958 - 4.1: 1950s
Anshe Emet Cinema Arts Festival, 1960 - 4.1: 1960
Aqueduct Art Gallery, New York, 1966 - 4.1: 1966
Area, "Art," New York, 1985 - 3.1: "Art", Group Exhibition at Area, 1985
L'art et L'automobile, automotive artists group exhibition, 1988 - 4.1: 1988
L'art et l'automobile, Ferrari Collection exhibition, 1989 - 4.1: 1989
Art Directors Club of Chicago, Exhibition of Advertising and Editorial Art, 1955 - 4.1: 1950s
Art Expo - 4.1: Undated
Art Institute of Chicago, Student Exhibition, 1950 - 4.1: 1950s
Art Institute of Chicago, Student Exhibition, 1951 - 4.1: 1950s
Art Institute of Chicago, "Artists of Chicago and Vicinity," 1953 - 4.1: 1950s
Art Institute of Chicago, Instructors Exhibition, 1955 - 3.1: Art Institute of Chicago Instructors Exhibition 1955
Art Institute of Chicago, "Artists of Chicago and Vicinity," 1956 - 4.1: 1950s
Art Institute of Chicago, American Painting and Sculpture, 1957 - 4.1: 1950s
Art Institute of Chicago, Instructors Exhibition, 1957 - 4.1: 1950s
Art Institute of Chicago, "Artists of Chicago and Vicinity," 1961 - 4.1: 1961
Art Institute of Chicago, "Drawing New Conclusions," 1992 - 3.1: "Drawing New Conclusions," Art Institute of Chicago group exhibition 1992
Baja Club, "Art's As Good An Investment as Bonds," New York, 1989 - 3.1: Baird Jones' Group Exhibitions 1988-89